today i am going to build 1 0 brownie mark.
come on,
this product has no differential.
this right here is 1 dull square chocolate cake
that everyone only invests in packaging.
difference is the flavors.
Is it on?
how do we sell brownie in a more
interesting and less interested?
I think I had 1 idea
for us to build this market differential
we're going to need the context.
calls doidão,
come with me, uncle,
I need to consider where I am,
bro,
what is the city,
local culture and behavior,
what they like to do,
which also has a connection
to be able to work with this brand.
Charlie Brown Junior,
man already has a more nostalgic attractive appeal.
and for you to keep a brand alive today
one must also attract the z generation.
and that's where the differential of my idea comes from.
and if I put 1 little more foam
in this here
I can make my mark more evident
and charge even more.
wants to see?
and if instead of us we make a square brownie,
we make a brownie in a circle
and that circle is an edible skate wheel?
and then I start to have a differential of my product.
now i only need 1 slogan.
Charlie Brown Junior,
an edible skate wheel
and the slogan is,
if not me,
who will make you happy.
that's the plan.
now I need to know how.
I do all this with less than a thousand reais
until tomorrow.
if that's not what will pass you're happy.
if that's not what will pass you by.